Anybody's not stuck. I'm not swimming.
Break it down, stop!
You can't do this. Watch me. Justice will prevail.
Main Dancer & Backup Vocal Group Super Tokkyu
Last year, the group added a new member, bringing the total number of members to nine.
The first album of the new group, B9, is finally completed!
I think you can see a completely different side of Chotokkyu.
I think we will be able to show you a more evolved version of Chotokkyu.
In order to deliver the further charm of the evolved Super Express to our fans
I'm sure we'll do something crazy.
I think it will be really cool with everyone in Hakkoichi.
I think the first word will probably change.
I'm really excited about the B9 production site.
Don't do that!
Lots of off-shoots!
Special delivery of 3 times in total
BEST9, a documentary closely followed by Chotoku Kyu
This time, we go behind the scenes of the music video for the new song
Moramora's music video shoot.
Let's do it once. Let's do it once.
What are the thoughts behind the new song?
I'm looking forward to working with you.
May I?
Happi Valentine!
Oh, really?
Oh no!
I didn't think so!
Cookies?
I made another batch a couple of days ago.
I made another batch of cookies a couple days ago.
So I made another batch.
I changed the menu.
I made these.
It didn't work.
Oh, no.
Can I go over it from the top?
Please!
B9, the first album under the new organization.
A new concept and a new theme.
It's just so cool.
Manly, cool, sexy.
It's a new weapon for us!
At the time of our debut
We were selling coolness when we debuted.
I think it's an album that reminds us of our original intentions.
And that's exactly what we've done now that we're 9 members.
And now that we have 9 members, each of us has a new personality
and performance skills
I think it will be an album that shines even brighter
I think this album will be an album where that shines through even more.
I felt it was very meaningful to do this album now.
I thought it would be a great album to express coolness in a simple way.
I think it will be a work that expresses coolness in a simple way.
I think it will be a work that expresses coolness in a pure way.
Up until now, Super Express has
High level performance with a comical side
with a comical side to their high-level performances
with a comical side to their high-level performances.
But
This time, the new album has a new point
The theme is Cool & Stylish
The song that symbolizes it
is the new song "Mora Mora".
In words, Mora Mora
In other words, "mora mora" means "to mora everything".
It's a little bit easy to understand such words
I've made the alphabet a little bit catchy
I'm trying to make it a little bit catchy.
What we want to mora for our listeners
What do we want to mora?
We want to mora everything about this person.
It can be used with this kind of meaning.
It's simple to listen to.
It's a little bit addictive, isn't it?
In order to find a new charm of KOTOKUQYU, all the members discussed and created the song from scratch.
We came up with a lot of ideas from the creation stage.
We came up with a lot of ideas.
The red balen of 2a wasn't included in the beginning, but I said I wanted to include it.
I said, "I want to put it in," and we came up with an interesting structure.
I was able to create a variety of interesting compositions, and I was able to create some tasty parts.When we were talking about teaching fridge instruction.
I was saying how nice it would be to have you as a mentor.
I said I thought it would be great for Kaita-san, and it turned out that way.
I didn't think he would do it, especially Masahiro Aloha Yuki, who was overjoyed.
The choreography was written by the first champion of the world's top dance league, the d-League.
He is one of the top dancers that Japan is proud of, who won the first d-league championship and has performed with big artists overseas.
He is one of the top dancers in Japan and has performed with big artists overseas.
Since the choreography was done by Mr. Writer, it's a bit like hip-hop in terms of genre.
The choreography is in the swanky style that's popular right now, so...
It's intense, and it's not too much to say that it's a dance number.
It's not an exaggeration to say that it's a dance number.
It's probably twice as strenuous as a normal song.
He's a security guard.
Whoo!
(Let's keep him close)
He's security
Let's go!
Once the difficult choreography is mastered, the filming of the music video will begin.
It's time to start shooting the music video.
I'm counting on you.
I'm looking forward to working with you!
This time, I suggested that the set, or rather the dancing area, be made to look like a music video using only lights, so that the dance and the costumes would look good, which I think is very impressive.
To make the dance look better, we paid attention to every detail, including the set, lighting, and costumes.
First, let's start with a one-shot image cut.
Oh, I like it here.
Sexy sexy sexy.
This is good.
That thing I was talking about earlier, like this.
What did I do?
That was good.
Okay, well, that's my best sexy sexy.
Your best?
Yes, ma'am.
ED.
SUBSCRIBE MY CHANNEL
Dada dancer, dada dancer, dada dancer
Burn it into your brain!
Behind the music video shooting, we also shot a video for TikTok!
Oh!
You!
Don't take my hand.
Oh!
I won't hold your hand.
Shuya's gonna be stuck in this bottle for the rest of his life.
He's stuck in the point where he can't do it.
He keeps making the same mistake over and over again.
And when he gets it right in the second half...
And when he could do the second half, he couldn't do the first half.
He was stuck in a loop for the rest of his life.
I probably lost.
Ha-ha-ha!
Wow!
No!
There you go. There you go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, wow.
Smile, smile, smile.
Smile.
Yeah.
Now one, two, three.
Now.
Now
UT werden
More TikTok videos with many variations of the new Mora Mora song to come!
Check it out!
And the shooting of all the boys together has started!
Preliminary vashon is also re-uploaded!
I knew it was good!
Lalala papiramicello dynamite!
Ladies and gentlemen, please let the play work flow over here at the base.
Check every single cut in detail.
Kania, I would be happy if you could take a look at the balance between Takashi and Shuya's shinmei in the chorus position, as it seems to be different.
Which one is better?
I heard that the one on the right is more beautiful.
For example, after this.
For example, here and here.
This one is open, but this one is quite full.This one is open here, but this one looks pretty packed.
This one might be better.
Then it spreads out.
I think it's really slightly.
Shuya pointed out the positions of the members.
This is one cut of the chorus where it is important to align everyone's dance.
We decided to redo it so that the left and right balances are perfectly aligned.
Can I just check that one time?
Yes.
I'm fired up, come on.
I'm sorry, can I just check the position of the chorus one time?
Yes.
You know what I mean?
I know it.
It needs to be a little wider.
That's good, right?
I want to go up and down again.
Let's go one more time.
I think my knee might be bent too much.
Maybe that one should be bent.
Up and down is not backwards.
I'm going to lean back a little bit.
Maybe I should just lean back a little bit.
I adjusted the slightest misalignment and repeated the shot many times.
This is not good!
Wow!
Even more...
Dada dada dada dada
It became tremendous!
I can do this.
Squats, right?
Can I try one?
No, not at all.
I'm good.
I want to hold it.
Yuki suggested changing the camerawork.
One time... oh, oh, oh, oh...
Ui
around the mouth
Match Yuki's hand movement
Swinging the camera up
The challenge of creating a sense of movement
New song
Latata Bamba Vina Vista and Dive
Latata Bamba Let it go
In a small place
Yeah, yeah, yeah, wake up
Here is the finished scene
Latata Bamba Vina Vista and Dive
Latata Bamba Let it go
In a small place
Latata Bamba Vina Vista and Dive
Latata Bamba Let it go
In a small place
Yeah
[Applause
And so the whole 12-hour shoot is over.
This time, we're really focusing on the 100 coolest parts of the film.
I'd be happy if you could pay attention to that.
I thought it was going to be one of my best works.
The filming went very well, just as I had hoped.
I think this song is a perfect example of the skills of each of the dancers.
Even professional dancers will think it's a cool type of music video.
I'm sure it will be a cool type of music video even for professional dancers.
I hope many artists and professional dancers will see it.
I hope many artists and professional dancers will watch it.
I think it's the hardest song in the super express market.
I think it's the hardest song in the market.
I think it will be a great spectacle.
And the way the dancers look when they dance together
I feel the way the dancers dance when they are all together
I think it's very powerful in the video.
I hope you will be fascinated by the music
I want to make it such a mora mora that people will come to see it a lot.
I want to make it such a mora mora that people will come to see.
I'd like to show our coolness by going back to the basics.
I'm personally very happy to be able to release our coolness on our first album after joining CM.
I'm personally very happy to be able to release this album.
I'm going to give my maximum performance as much as I can.
I'm sure I'll give this performance at the live show as well.I'm sure we will give this performance at the live show as well.
Please look forward to it!
I thought my sense of unity was suddenly quite strong.
I was watching and watching the video.
I mean, everyone was really mollified.
I could really see everyone's one hot and burning spirit.
I was really looking forward to the future.
It was a music video that made me want to do even more.
I've never seen a music video that made me feel like this.
Thank you very much.
We all got it!
We got it so much!
I think it's really cool to see the 9 of you in every corner of the room.
I'm sure you'll be able to see the 9 of us in all our coolness.
Please watch it again and again!
The music video, filled with the passion and direction of the members, is now available on our official YouTube channel!
You can watch it on their official YouTube channel!
Don't miss it!
You've got the last word, don't you?
For now.
I wanted the four new members to produce it.
Of course, we need to change the video and create a buzz there.
It's just not realistic.
If you've got something, just one thing.
I'd like to see something that says, "This is all I've got.
Next episode preview